Department of Archaeology fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
Department of Archaeology fonds
1966 - 1986
F-4
3.5 m of textual records
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department Maggie Benston Student Services Building, Rm. 0400 8888 University Dr. Burnaby British Columbia Canada V5A 1S6 Telephone: 778.782.3805 Email: archives@sfu.ca http://www.sfu.ca/archives
Department of Archaeology
The Department of Archaeology was originally established in 1965 as a program area within the Department of Political Science, Sociology and Anthropology (P.S.A.). In 1969, the Department was removed from P.S.A. to become an independent unit within the Faculty of Arts. In 1971, it became a full Department. The Department is responsible, through its Chair, for the promotion of research and the development and delivery of programs in the field of Archaeology. The Department is involved in interdisciplinary programs both within the University and with external bodies, including the Institute for Quaternary Research (IQR) and Continuing Studies and Distance Education programs.
The Department is organized administratively into a Chair, Departmental Assistant, and a number of standing committees. The Chair is the chief administrative officer, whose responsibilities include the management of the operational budget; faculty tenure, promotion and salary recommendations; teaching assignments, and representation of the Department to external bodies, including the Faculty, Senate and Board of Governors. The Chair reports directly to the Dean of Arts. The Departmental Assistant is responsible for much of the day-to-day administration and the management of the departmental budget, the scheduling of courses, the provision of liaison with administrative offices, and advising students. The Department also comprises the Museum of Archaeology and Ethnology, and the Radiocarbon Laboratory. The Museum Curator and Laboratory Manager reports directly to the Chair of the Department, who is the Director of each of these units and is therefore responsible for fiscal, administrative, and academic matters pertaining to them.
The number and composition of departmental committees varied greatly over time. Long-standing committees include Appointments, Graduate Studies, Undergraduate Curriculum, and Tenure. There is also departmental representation on faculty and university committees, including the Faculty of Arts Curriculum committee and the University's Articulation committee. The Department also struck ad hoc committees, such as the Chairman's Search Committee, when required.
published
Full
Revised
Title of the fonds is based on the name of the body.
The fonds of the Department of Archaeology consists of records created and received in the course of the administration of the Department and the carrying out of its functions of providing instruction and promoting research. The activities documented include policy and procedures development; the planning, initiation and administration of curriculum and programs; departmental and faculty meetings; faculty salary, appointment, promotion and tenure deliberations; departmental reviews; and the publication of journals and reports. The types of documents include meeting agenda, correspondence, course outlines and examinations, an external review, faculty case files, memoranda, agenda and minutes of meetings, and reports.
The materials were arranged by the archivist in 1989, with an accrual in 2003.
Shutler, Richard, Jr.; Carlson, Roy L.
The records were transferred in a number of annual accessions from the Department, beginning in 1981.
As of January 2012, 33 cm of additional material have been accessioned but not yet processed. Please consult an archivist for information about using these materials; restrictions may apply. Further accruals are expected.
Consult the inventory to the Department of Political Science, Sociology and Anthropology fonds, F-20. Also consult the inventory to the Faculty of Arts fonds, F-2.
Some files may contain personal or confidential information. Access to these files may be restricted as required by law. Files marked 'pending review' must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release, and as a result of the review access restrictions may apply. Please see the file lists and consult the archivist for more details.
File lists are available.
- Departmental history, 1970 - 1985; F-4-1; 12 cm of textual records
  published
  Series consists of records relating to the establishment of the department and its history. It includes proposals, reports, and a history of the department by Kristine Andersen (1985).
  Kristine Andersen
  - Establishment of department, 1971; F-4-1-0-0-1 (Archival box - small 4-1)
    Textual records
    Pending review
  - History of the Department, 1974; F-4-1-0-0-2 (Archival box - small 4-1)
  - Department Proposals, 1970 - 1974; F-4-1-0-0-3 (Archival box - small 4-1)
  - History by K. Andersen, 1985; F-4-1-0-0-4 (Archival box - small 4-1)
    Open
- Correspondence, 1967 - 1986; F-4-2; 1.13 m of textual records
  Series consists of correspondence and related materials received and sent by the Chair. It includes correspondence, journals, memoranda, and reports.
  Series arranged by the archivist in 1989.
  As part of the 1994 records centre cleanout and appraisal project, the archivist added file F-4-2-3-0-1 to the fonds.
  A file list is available.
  - Chronological correspondence, 1969 - 1980; F-4-2-1; 54 cm of textual records
    - Chronological Correspondence, 1969; F-4-2-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 4-2)
    - Chronological Correspondence, 1970; F-4-2-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 4-2)
    - Chronological Correspondence, 1971; F-4-2-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 4-2)
    - Chronological Correspondence, 1972; F-4-2-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 4-2)
    - Chronological Correspondence, 1973; F-4-2-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 4-2)
    - Chronological Correspondence, 1973; F-4-2-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 4-3)
    - Chronological Correspondence, 1974; F-4-2-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 4-3)
    - Chronological Correspondence, 1974; F-4-2-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 4-3)
    - Chronological Correspondence, 1975; F-4-2-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 4-3)
    - Chronological Correspondence, 1975; F-4-2-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 4-3)
    - Chronological Correspondence, 1976; F-4-2-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 4-4)
    - Chronological Correspondence, 1976; F-4-2-1-0-12 (Archival box - standard 4-4)
    - Chronological Correspondence, 1977; F-4-2-1-0-13 (Archival box - standard 4-4)
    - Chronological Correspondence, 1977; F-4-2-1-0-14 (Archival box - standard 4-4)
    - Chronological Correspondence, 1978; F-4-2-1-0-15 (Archival box - standard 4-5)
    - Chronological Correspondence, 1978; F-4-2-1-0-16 (Archival box - standard 4-5)
    - Chronological Correspondence, 1979; F-4-2-1-0-17 (Archival box - standard 4-5)
    - Chronological Correspondence, 1979; F-4-2-1-0-18 (Archival box - standard 4-5)
    - Chronological Correspondence, 1980; F-4-2-1-0-19 (Archival box - standard 4-6)
    - Chronological Correspondence, 1980; F-4-2-1-0-20 (Archival box - standard 4-6)
  - Memoranda, 1967 - 1983; F-4-2-2; 59 cm of textual records
    Faculty of Arts and Social Sciences; Office of the Dean of Graduate Studies; African and Middle East Studies; Centre for Canadian Studies; Continuing Studies; Department of Spanish and Latin American Studies; University Advancement; Centre for Online and Distance Education; National Film Board; National Museums of Canada Corporation; University of Calgary. Department of Archaeology; Union of British Columbia Indian Chiefs; Office of the President; Office of the Vice-President, Academic and Provost
    - Memoranda, 1968 - 1974; F-4-2-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 4-6)
    - Dean of Arts, 1969 - 1978; F-4-2-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 4-6)
    - Dean of Graduate Studies, 1969 - 1978; F-4-2-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 4-6)
    - V.P.'s and President, 1972 - 1978; F-4-2-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 4-6)
    - Chair, 1979; F-4-2-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 4-7)
    - Africa and Middle East Studies, 1969 - 1972; F-4-2-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 4-7)
    - Africa and Middle East Studies, 1973 - 1977; F-4-2-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 4-7)
    - Canadian Studies, 1969 - 1977; F-4-2-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 4-7)
    - Canadian Studies, 1978 - 1979; F-4-2-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 4-7)
    - Continuing Studies, 1971 - 1973; F-4-2-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 4-7)
    - Continuing Studies, 1974 - 1976; F-4-2-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 4-7)
    - Continuing Studies (B.C. Studies), 1975 - 1978; F-4-2-2-0-12 (Archival box - standard 4-7)
    - Latin America Studies, 1969 - 1977; F-4-2-2-0-13 (Archival box - standard 4-8)
    - Resources Office, 1974 - 1978; F-4-2-2-0-14 (Archival box - standard 4-8)
    - B.C. Studies Magazine, 1970 - 1974; F-4-2-2-0-15 (Archival box - standard 4-8)
    - B.C. Studies Magazine (Special Issue), 1970; F-4-2-2-0-16 (Archival box - standard 4-8)
    - Bill C-33, 1976; F-4-2-2-0-17 (Archival box - standard 4-8)
    - Carbon Dating Facility, 1967 - 1973; F-4-2-2-0-18 (Archival box - standard 4-8)
    - Carbon Dating Facility, 1974 - 1978; F-4-2-2-0-19 (Archival box - standard 4-8)
    - Distance Education, 1977 - 1978; F-4-2-2-0-20 (Archival box - standard 4-8)
    - Friends of S.F.U., 1972 - 1975; F-4-2-2-0-21 (Archival box - standard 4-8)
    - Graduate Students, 1974 - 1977; F-4-2-2-0-22 (Archival box - standard 4-9)
    - Graduate Student Supervision, 1978 - 1982; F-4-2-2-0-23 (Archival box - standard 4-9)
    - Instruction Activity Analysis, 1976 - 1979; F-4-2-2-0-24 (Archival box - standard 4-9)
    - M.P.X. Original Plans, 1976 - 1979; F-4-2-2-0-25 (Archival box - standard 4-9)
    - M.P.X. Extension, 1978 - 1983; F-4-2-2-0-26 (Archival box - standard 4-9)
    - National Film Board, 1975 - 1976; F-4-2-2-0-27 (Archival box - standard 4-9)
    - National Museum, 1970 - 1978; F-4-2-2-0-28 (Archival box - standard 4-9)
    - Sisiutl, Research Vessel, 1971 - 1976; F-4-2-2-0-29 (Archival box - standard 4-10)
    - Space Requirements, 1968 - 1976; F-4-2-2-0-30 (Archival box - standard 4-10)
    - Speakers, 1967 - 1977; F-4-2-2-0-31 (Archival box - standard 4-10)
    - University of Calgary Archaeology Review, 1977 - 1978; F-4-2-2-0-32 (Archival box - standard 4-10)
    - Union of B.C. Indians, 1970 - 1975; F-4-2-2-0-33 (Archival box - standard 4-10)
  - Correspondence, 1981 - 1986; F-4-2-3; 2 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence -- Jon Driver, Chair of Graduate Program committee, 1981 - 1986; F-4-2-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 4-6)
- Faculty members, 1967 - 1986; F-4-3; 40 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records related to faculty members, including research grant files, and correspondence with Canada Council and the President's Research Grant Committee. Record types include correspondence, memoranda, and reports.
  Canada Council for the Arts; President's Research Grant Committee
  As part of the 1994 records centre cleanout and appraisal project, the archivist added file F-4-3-0-0-23 to the fonds.
  Access to records related to faculty tenure and appointments, case files, is restricted in accordance with Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy legislation. Consult the unit list and the archivist for further information.
  - Tenured Faculty, 1970 - 1976; F-4-3-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 4-11)
  - Salary Review, 1975 - 1977; F-4-3-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 4-11)
  - Faculty: Salary Review, 1972 - 1982; F-4-3-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 4-11)
  - Canada Council, 1970 - 1979; F-4-3-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 4-11)
  - President's Research Grants, 1967 - 1974; F-4-3-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 4-11)
  - President's Research Grants, 1975 - 1977; F-4-3-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 4-11)
  - Faculty - K, 1969 - 1978; F-4-3-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 4-11)
  - Faculty - H, 1978 - 1979; F-4-3-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 4-11)
  - FacultY - H, 1968 - 1976; F-4-3-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 4-11)
  - Faculty - H, 1977 - 1980; F-4-3-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 4-12)
  - Faculty - N, 1972 - 1977; F-4-3-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 4-12)
  - Faculty - N, 1978 - 1980; F-4-3-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 4-12)
  - Faculty - N, 1974 - 1975; F-4-3-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 4-12)
  - Faculty - N, 1976 - 1977; F-4-3-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 4-12)
  - Faculty - N, 1978 - 1980; F-4-3-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 4-12)
  - Faculty - S, 1975 - 1977; F-4-3-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 4-13)
  - Faculty - S, 1978 - 1979; F-4-3-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 4-13)
  - Faculty - S, 1980 - 1981; F-4-3-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 4-13)
  - Faculty - A, 1968 - 1975; F-4-3-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 4-13)
  - Faculty - A, 1976 - 1979; F-4-3-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 4-13)
  - Faculty - A, 1980 - 1983; F-4-3-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 4-14)
  - Faculty - M, 1971 - 1974; F-4-3-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 4-14)
  - Faculty teaching and research, 1974 - 1986; F-4-3-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 4-14)
- Departmental committees, 1969 - 1986; F-4-4; 9 cm of textual records
  Series consists of the records of various departmental committees, including the Appointments, Graduate Studies, and Tenure committees. It includes circulars, correspondence, minutes of meetings, and memoranda.
  Department of Archaeology. Appointments Committee; Department of Archaeology. Departmental Tenure Committee; Graduate Studies Committee
  As part of the 1994 records centre cleanout and appraisal project, the archivist added file F-4-4-0-0-10 to the fonds.
  Access to records related to appointments and the Appointment committee is restricted in accordance with Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy legislation. Consult the unit list and the archivist for further information.
  - Appointment Committee, 1974 - 1979; F-4-4-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 4-14)
  - Appointments - H, 1974; F-4-4-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 4-14)
  - Appointments - N, 1974; F-4-4-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 4-14)
  - Appointments - N, 1975; F-4-4-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 4-14)
  - Appointments - C, 1976; F-4-4-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 4-14)
  - Appointment - K, 1977; F-4-4-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 4-14)
  - Graduate Studies Committee, 1976 - 1978; F-4-4-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 4-14)
  - Graduate Studies Committee, 1979 - 1980; F-4-4-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 4-14)
  - Tenure Committee, 1969 - 1977; F-4-4-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 4-14)
  - Graduate Program committee - minutes, 1979 - 1986; F-4-4-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 4-14)
- Faculty committees, 1968 - 1978; F-4-5; 4 cm of textual records
  Series consists of the records relating to faculty committees which had departmental representation, including the Committee for Extension Credit and the Curriculum Committee. The series includes correspondence.
  Faculty of Arts. Advisory Committee on Extension Credit Programs; Faculty of Arts. Curriculum Committee
  - Faculty of Arts: Committee for Extension Credit, 1976 - 1978; F-4-5-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 4-14)
  - Faculty of Arts: Curriculum Committee, 1968 - 1977; F-4-5-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 4-15)
- University committees, 1976 - 1978; F-4-6; 5 cm of textual records
  Series consists of the records relating to the Sociology / Anthropology Articulation Committee (representing Sociology and Anthropology departments in BC universities and community colleges), and SFU's Senate Committee on Admissions and Standings.
  Sociology / Anthropology Articulation Committee; Senate Committee on Admissions and Standings
  - Articulation Committee, 1976 - 1978; F-4-6-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 4-15)
  - Senate Committee on Admissions and Standings, 1976 - 1978; F-4-6-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 4-15)
- Departmental reviews, 1975; F-4-7; 5 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to an external review of the Department conducted in 1975. It includes correspondence, memoranda, and reports.
  - External Review Information, 1975; F-4-7-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 4-15)
  - External Review, 1975; F-4-7-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 4-15)
- Course outlines and examinations, 1966 - 1986; F-4-8; 1.04 m of textual records
  Series consists of undergraduate and graduate course outlines, graduate examinations, and new course proposals.
  Files are arranged chronologically.
  As part of the 1994 records centre cleanout and appraisal project, the archivist added numerous course files (from 1980 to 1986) to the fonds.
  - Course Outline, 101-3, 1971 - 1979; F-4-8-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 4-16)
  - Course Outline, 131-3, 1975 - 1979; F-4-8-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 4-16)
  - Course Outline, 223-3, 1974 - 1978; F-4-8-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 4-16)
  - Course Outline, 272-3, 1966 - 1979; F-4-8-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 4-16)
  - Course Outline, 273-3, 1967 - 1979; F-4-8-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 4-16)
  - Course Outline, 301-2, 1972 - 1979; F-4-8-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 4-16)
  - Course Outline, 330-5, 1975 - 1979; F-4-8-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 4-16)
  - Course Outline, 333-3, 1976 - 1979; F-4-8-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 4-16)
  - Course Outline, 335-5, 1976 - 1977; F-4-8-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 4-16)
  - Course Outline, 340-3, 1977 - 1979; F-4-8-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 4-16)
  - Course Outline, 360-5, 1974 - 1978; F-4-8-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 4-17)
  - Course Outline, 365-5, 1976 - 1979; F-4-8-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 4-17)
  - Course Outline, 370-5, 1977 - 1978; F-4-8-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 4-17)
  - Course Outline, 371-5, 1973 - 1979; F-4-8-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 4-17)
  - Course Outline, 372-5, 1970 - 1979; F-4-8-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 4-17)
  - Course Outline, 373-5, 1972 - 1979; F-4-8-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 4-17)
  - Course Outline, 374-5, 1975; F-4-8-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 4-17)
  - Course Outline, 375-5, 1971; F-4-8-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 4-17)
  - Course Outline, 376-5, 1975 - 1979; F-4-8-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 4-17)
  - Course Outline, 385-3, 1972 - 1979; F-4-8-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 4-17)
  - Course Outline, 410-5, 1976 - 1979; F-4-8-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 4-18)
  - Course Outline, 411-5, 1976 - 1979; F-4-8-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 4-18)
  - Course Outline, 432-5, 1976 - 1979; F-4-8-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 4-18)
  - Course Outline, 438-3, 1975 - 1979; F-4-8-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 4-18)
  - Course Outline, 439-3, 1973 - 1979; F-4-8-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 4-18)
  - Course Outline, 440-3, 1978 - 1979; F-4-8-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 4-18)
  - Course Outline, 442-5, 1982; F-4-8-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 4-18)
  - Course Outline, 472-3, 1969; F-4-8-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 4-18)
  - Course Outline, 473-5, 1968 - 1978; F-4-8-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 4-18)
  - Course Outline, 474-5, 1972 - 1977; F-4-8-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 4-18)
  - Course Outline, 475-5, 1971 - 1979; F-4-8-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 4-18)
  - Course Outline, 476-5, 1971 - 1979; F-4-8-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 4-18)
  - Course Outline, 480-5, 1974 - 1979; F-4-8-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 4-18)
  - Course Outline, 493-5, 1968 - 1979; F-4-8-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 4-18)
  - Course Outline, 499-5, 1975 - 1978; F-4-8-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 4-18)
  - Course Outline, 840, 1978; F-4-8-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 4-18)
  - Course Outline, 871, 1974; F-4-8-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 4-18)
  - Course Outline, 876, 1978; F-4-8-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 4-18)
  - Course Outline, 881-5, 1977; F-4-8-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 4-18)
  - Course Outline, 883-5, 1975; F-4-8-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 4-18)
  - Course Outline, 895-5, 1974 - 1978; F-4-8-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 4-18)
  - Course Outline, 896-5, 1974 - 1976; F-4-8-0-0-42 (Archival box - standard 4-18)
  - ARC 898-5 (no course outline available), 1976 - 1979; F-4-8-0-0-43 (Archival box - standard 4-19)
  - ARC 899-5 (no course outline available), 1976 - 1978; F-4-8-0-0-44 (Archival box - standard 4-19)
  - Graduate Courses, 1973 - 1979; F-4-8-0-0-45 (Archival box - standard 4-19)
  - Graduate Examinations (none available), 1976 - 1979; F-4-8-0-0-46 (Archival box - standard 4-19)
  - New Course Proposals, 1973 - 1979; F-4-8-0-0-47 (Archival box - standard 4-19)
  - ARC 101-3 The Prehistoric Past, 1980 - 1981; F-4-8-0-0-48 (Archival box - standard 4-24)
  - ARC 131-3 Human Origins, 1980 - 1981; F-4-8-0-0-49 (Archival box - standard 4-24)
  - ARC 223-3 The Prehistory of Canada, 1980 - 1981; F-4-8-0-0-50 (Archival box - standard 4-24)
  - ARC 272-3 Archaeology of the Old World, 1980 - 1981; F-4-8-0-0-51 (Archival box - standard 4-24)
  - ARC 273-3 Archaeology of the New World, 1980 - 1981; F-4-8-0-0-52 (Archival box - standard 4-24)
  - ARC 301-2 Prehistoric and Primitive Art, 1980 - 1981; F-4-8-0-0-53 (Archival box - standard 4-24)
  - ARC 330-3 Prehistory of Latin America, Peru - Campus, 1980 - 1981; F-4-8-0-0-54 (Archival box - standard 4-24)
  - ARC 332-3 Special Topics Prehistory of South and East Asia, 1981; F-4-8-0-0-55 (Archival box - standard 4-24)
  - ARC 333-3 Special Topics: South America, 1980 - 1981; F-4-8-0-0-56 (Archival box - standard 4-24)
  - ARC 334-3 Special Topics: Introduction to Classical Archaeology, 1981; F-4-8-0-0-57 (Archival box - standard 4-24)
  - ARC 335-5 Special Topics: Stone Tool Analysis, 1980 - 1981; F-4-8-0-0-58 (Archival box - standard 4-24)
  - ARC 340-3 Introductory Zooarchaeology, 1980 - 1981; F-4-8-0-0-59 (Archival box - standard 4-24)
  - ARC 360-5 Indian Cultures of North America, 1980 - 1981; F-4-8-0-0-60 (Archival box - standard 4-24)
  - ARC 365-5 Ecological Archaeology, 1980 - 1981; F-4-8-0-0-61 (Archival box - standard 4-24)
  - ARC 370-3 Western Pacific Prehistory, 1980 - 1981; F-4-8-0-0-62 (Archival box - standard 4-24)
  - ARC 371-5 Archaeological Theory, 1981; F-4-8-0-0-63 (Archival box - standard 4-24)
  - ARC 372-5 Archaeology Lab Techniques, 1980 - 1981; F-4-8-0-0-64 (Archival box - standard 4-24)
  - ARC 373-5 Human Osteology, 1980 - 1981; F-4-8-0-0-65 (Archival box - standard 4-24)
  - ARC 376-5 Quantitative Methods in Archaeology, 1980 - 1981; F-4-8-0-0-66 (Archival box - standard 4-24)
  - ARC 385-3 Fossil Man, 1980 - 1981; F-4-8-0-0-67 (Archival box - standard 4-24)
  - ARC 410-5 Advanced Archeometry, 1980 - 1981; F-4-8-0-0-68 (Archival box - standard 4-24)
  - ARC 411-5 Archaeological Dating, 1980 - 1981; F-4-8-0-0-69 (Archival box - standard 4-24)
  - ARC 432-5 Advanced Physical Anthropology, 1980 - 1981; F-4-8-0-0-70 (Archival box - standard 4-24)
  - ARC 433-5, 434-5,435-2, 436-3 Field School - Kwatna, 1980 - 1981; F-4-8-0-0-71 (Archival box - standard 4-25)
  - ARC 438-3 Application to Sedimentology to Archaeology, 1980; F-4-8-0-0-72 (Archival box - standard 4-25)
  - ARC 439-3 Early Man and Environments in North America, 1980 - 1981; F-4-8-0-0-73 (Archival box - standard 4-25)
  - ARC 440-3 Advanced Zooarchaeology, 1980 - 1981; F-4-8-0-0-74 (Archival box - standard 4-25)
  - ARC 473-3 Prehistory of Africa, 1980; F-4-8-0-0-75 (Archival box - standard 4-25)
  - ARC 474-5 Archaeology of the Southwest (North America), 1980 - 1981; F-4-8-0-0-76 (Archival box - standard 4-25)
  - ARC 475-5 North America - Arctic, 1980 - 1981; F-4-8-0-0-77 (Archival box - standard 4-25)
  - ARC 476-5 Prehistory of Northwest Pacific, 1980; F-4-8-0-0-78 (Archival box - standard 4-25)
  - ARC 480-5 Directed Readings, 1980 - 1981; F-4-8-0-0-79 (Archival box - standard 4-25)
  - ARC 499-5 Honors Essay, 1980; F-4-8-0-0-80 (Archival box - standard 4-25)